[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Skin consists of how many basic layers?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "5", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Paul Erdos (pronounced Irr-dish) was a Hungarian mathematician with a very peculiar trait. What is it?", "correct_answer": "He has said that he prefers mathematics to sex.", "incorrect_answers": ["He memorized all the prime numbers from 2 through 5,986,771,223", "He is the only mathematician to have won an Oscar.", "He is a self-taught mathematician - he wrote his Doctor thesis without ever taking a course in any college."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only US state to have two Ivy League colleges in it ?", "correct_answer": "New York", "incorrect_answers": ["Connecticut", "New Jersey", "Massachusetts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is an eponym meaning a traitor to his country?", "correct_answer": "A quisling", "incorrect_answers": ["A McCarthy", "A cyrano", "A ruy lopez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Barry wrote the music of the theme song for the James Bond movie Goldfinger. Which singer became famous for performing the song and sold more than a million copies of it in the USA alone?", "correct_answer": "Shirley Bassey", "incorrect_answers": ["Dusty Springfield", "Joni Mitchell", "Mariska Veres"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fish taco is generally cooked by what method?", "correct_answer": "Frying", "incorrect_answers": ["Broiling", "Baking", "Poaching"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Purple is the official color of what Hawaiian Island?", "correct_answer": "Kauai", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Lanai", "Maui"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A polar bear has white fur.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a Polish beer brand, established in 1629?", "correct_answer": "Tyskie", "incorrect_answers": ["Saku", "Kalnapilis", "A. Le Coq"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The color called sepia is a shade of this color.", "correct_answer": "Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver", "Navy", "Plum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of alcohol is used as a base to make the popular Manhattan cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Whiskey", "incorrect_answers": ["Gin", "Rum", "Vodka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what internal human organ are the islets of Langerhans located?", "correct_answer": "Pancreas", "incorrect_answers": ["Spleen", "Liver", "Kidney"]}]